soloseo.com 2011-12-31

# Privacy Policy | SoloSEO

## Privacy Policy Statement

We collect contact information of those who contact us via e-mail, through contact forms, or registrations. We collect aggregate information on what pages and tools consumers access or visit, and information volunteered by the consumer (such as survey information and/or site registrations). This collected information is used to improve the content of our web site and quality of service, and is not shared, sold, or rented to other organizations for commercial purposes, except to provide products or services when we have your permission or under the following circumstances:

  * It is necessary to share information in order to investigate, prevent, or take action regarding illegal activities, suspected fraud, situations involving potential threats to the physical safety of any person, violations of Terms of Service, or as otherwise required by law. 
  * We transfer information about you if SoloSEO is acquired by or merged with another company. In this event, SoloSEO will notify you before information about you is transferred and becomes subject to a different privacy policy. 

#### Information Gathering and Use

  * When you register for a free trial or sign up for an account we ask for information such as your name, email, phone, billing address, and credit card information. Free trial accounts do not require a credit card. 
  * SoloSEO uses collected information for the following general purposes: products and services provision, billing, identification and authentication, services improvement, contact, and research. 

#### Cookies

  * Cookies contain small amounts of data, typically an anonymous unique identifier, that is sent to your browser from a web site server and stored on your computer's hard drive. 
  * Cookies are required to use the SoloSEO Service. 
  * You may be required to log-in after a certain period of time has elapsed to protect you against others accidentally accessing your account contents. 

#### Data Storage

  * You retain all rights to your data. SoloSEO owns the data storage, databases and all rights to the SoloSEO Service. 
  * We will never sell or share client data to any third-party. 
  * Your websites, projects, and related data, URLs, and other information is kept strictly confidential. 
  * We respect your privacy and the privacy of any websites you manage for your clients. 

#### Disclosure

SoloSEO may disclose personally identifiable information only under special circumstances such as to comply with subpoenas or when your actions violate the Terms of Service.

#### Changes to Privacy Policy

SoloSEO may periodically update this policy. We will notify paying customers of significant changes by sending a notice to the account email address or by placing a prominent notice on our site. 

#### Questions

Any questions about this Privacy Policy should be addressed by email to support at soloseo dot com.
